Sara|"What brings you to my Inn, young miss"|0|R
Breya|"I was told by Mr. Soren that you could help me get into the city"|1|L
|"The Inkeeper turned silent for a few moments"|0|R
Sara|"Be careful speaking about the city, girl?"|0|R
Sara|"Why do you want to know about the city anyways?"|0|R
Breya|"That is my own business"|1|L
Sara|"Hmph right. Well, it will be my business to help you or not"|0|R
Breya|"I have to go there to save my friend. She was taken"|1|L
Sara|"Come back once the patrons are gone"|0|R
Breya|"Yes Ma'am! Thank you so much"|1|L
|"Press ENTER to Continue.."|0|L